<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">101:Count of cards</string>
    <string name="ver">ver.0.2</string>

    <string name="count_score">Count the points</string>
    <string name="clear">New game</string>

    <string name="welcome_text">Welcome to the program scoring of the game 101! To start the game, select the number of participants:</string>
    <string name="win_text">Congratilation!   Winner:</string>

    <string name="two_player">Two\n players</string>
    <string name="three_player">Three\n players</string>
    <string name="four_player">Four\n players</string>
    <string name="five_player">Five\n players</string>
    <string name="game_rules">Game rules</string>

    <string name="two_game_title">101: game for two</string>
    <string name="three_game_title">101: game for three</string>
    <string name="four_game_title">101: game for four</string>
    <string name="five_game_title">101: game for five</string>

    <string name="input_name">Enter names of players In fields bellow and click \"Continue\"</string>
    <string name="info_player_1">1\'st player name</string>
    <string name="info_player_2">2\'nd  player name</string>
    <string name="info_player_3">3\'rd player name</string>
    <string name="info_player_4">4\'th player name</string>
    <string name="info_player_5">5\'th player name</string>

    <string name="player_name_hint">Enter name</string>

    <string name="Next">Continue</string>
    <string name="Begin">To beginning</string>
    <string name="GameRulesTitle">Game rules</string>
    <string name="GameRulesFullList">
        Play a deck of cards of 36 cards.\n
4 cards are dealt for each player, and to dealer - 3 cards (the fourth card he puts at stake).\n
The deck is placed in the middle of the table. \n
In the first game, the first move is given to dealer, and then to the player
        who won in the last game.\n
The player after the handler needs to beat the card on the stake. In this game going clockwise.\n
The next player can put on it a card of the same suit or the same dignity.\n
If he does not have the required card, he can take only one card, and he can still use the card
        from his arsenal - if it does not fit, the move goes to the next player.\n
If the cards in the deck end, the top and remaining under the table top are removed from
        the stack of open cards, the rest are turned over and again serve as a deck.\n\n
Special cards require certain actions from the following player:\n\n
6 - the player who was like should " to cover" it - put the card there, rule rules (if there are no
        suitable ones, take from the deck until he finds the right one).\n
7 - The next player must take 2 cards and skip the turn.\n
8 - the next player must take 1 card and skip the turn.\n
Ace - the next player misses the turn.\n
Queen is a trump card. A player who has laid out Queen can order any suit.
        The next player, in this case, can put the card only of the ordered suit or Queen
        (and order any suit).\n
King of Spades - The next player must take 4 cards and skip the turn.\n\n
The goal of one game stake is to get rid of all the cards on hand.
        The first player who gets rid of his cards wins.
        The rest count the points on the cards left in their hands.\n\n
Loses the one who collects more than 101 points.
    </string>
    <string name="GameRulesShortList">
        Briefly:\n
        6 - necessary "to cover" yourself.\n
        7 - the next one takes 2 cards and skips.\
        8 - the next one takes 1 card and skips.\n
        Ace - the next misses.\n
        The lady is a trump card.\n
        King of spades - the next takes 4 cards and skips.</string>
    <string name="PriceTitle">Points of cards</string>
    <string name="PriceList">Points are calculated according to the value of the card:\n
        Six - 6 points,\n
        Seven - 7 points,\n
        Eight - 8 points,\n
        Nine - 9 points,\n
        Ten - 10 points,\n
        Jack - 2 points,\n
        Queen - 3 points,\n
        King - 4 points,\n
        Ace - 11 points,\n\n
        If there is only:\n
        Queen of Spades - 40 points,\n
        Queen (not Spades) - 20 points,\n\n
        If the player puts the last:\n
        Queen of Spades - -40 points,\n
        Queen (not Spades) - -20 points.\n
    </string>

    <string name="TOAST_INPUT_FIELDS">Empty fields!</string>
    <string name="TOAST_TO_ZERO"> resets result!</string>
    <string name="total">Total</string>
    <string name="DOUBLE_PRESS_BACK">Press once again to exit</string>
    <string name="WELCOME_EXIT">Exit: May be no?</string>
    <string name="WELCOME_YES">I want exit, now!</string>
    <string name="WELCOME_NO">Okay, let\'s play again</string>
</resources>